http://www.labelapeel.co.uk/privacy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This policy statement explains how Label Apeel Ltd. will process your personal information. Our full company name is Label Apeel Limited and our registered office is James House, Murrayfield Road, Leicester LE3 1UW
What we collect, how and whyOur website uses forms that visitors can use to contact us or subscribe for email updates. We treat all your personal data with care and respect, and we're committed to industry best practice approaches concerning security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information in our possession.
Information handlingWe may disclose your information to companies who process data on our behalf, to our professional advisers, or when we are required by law to make such disclosures.
On all of our marketing communications you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications in the future. If you'd rather we didn't use your data for marketing purposes please contact us.
Most of our data is stored on our servers in the United Kingdom, although newsletter subscribers are stored outside the European Union.
Information requestsYou have a right to ask for a copy of your information (for which we charge a small fee) and to ask us to correct any inaccuracies in your personal information (which is free).
Notification of changesFrom time to time, we may update our Privacy Policy. This may be in relation to changes in the law, best practice or changes in our services.
Subscribe for email updates
Your Email
We always treat your personal data with care and respect.
